ICICI Lombard is also
showing some action. Vishwesh ji, please
take a look at the chart of ICICI Lombard. Sir, in the recent two-three days, there has been some
movement in some insurance stocks as well.
What would be your opinion on ICICI Lombard?
Deepanshu, it is moving from lower levels, it is
moving with very good support and overall
in insurance stocks, I feel that
a downside cap will be considered but
comparative to the market, I think
you will understand that some
supply is going to come in all these stocks on pullback,
so a time wise correction is pending.
Bank Nifty, which I had remarked at yesterday's closing, is in the
range of 52,200,300
and today also we are stuck there. Right now the
put writers of 52,000 have been trapped, so I think
you will find lower levels again in all the strong stocks.
ICICI, Lord,
ADAC Life are all good stocks.
I think if ICICI Lombard
particularly reaches the level of 1900, then we can consider it
for trading.  But overall the
support for 200 is around 1840, so
this is the opinion for you,
take IC and